copymoz.com 2012-12-27

# %%term_title%% » Copymoz

## Our Commitment

We recognize that your privacy is important. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use copymoz.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

Copymoz strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting customers, clients and online visitors privacy on this website.

#####  **Personal Information**

Copymoz collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, or company name, or telephone number. This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest, or sign up to join our email list, or request some other service, or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be provided to third parties under any circumstances.

#####  **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

This is a family website. We operate our site in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

#####  **Non-Personal Information**

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

#####  **Release of Information**

If Copymoz is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

#####  **How You Can Correct or Remove Information**

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact page.

#####  **Updates**

Notwithstanding Copymoz reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices has changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy if so needed. 

#####  **Agreeing to Terms**

If you do not agree to Copymoz Privacy Policy as posted here, notify us. Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

 **Meet Our Writer:** Cari - the CopyMoz author also writes content for three other websites. She has been writing on the internet since 2003; an original writer’s voice, engaging, entertaining and motivating the reader. Cari is an alumnus of the University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), San Fernando Valley Community College and William Howard Taft High School. [+Cari Mostert](https://plus.google.com/117190486790182374398/about?rel=author)
